Privacy Policy
==============

1\. General
-----------

By accessing or using the Tembo platform you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to update our privacy policy. The Tembo App and online services are built as a freemium service, meaning the app is provided at no cost, subject to advertising and optional in-app purchases/subscriptions. This service is provided as-is, and not subject to warranty.

2\. Information we collect
--------------------------

**Registration Data**: Information you provide through the registration process, including email address, this data is used to uniquely identify you as a user and associate your learning data with you. Additionally, where consent is given your email address may be used to deliver marketing and platform update correspondence.

**Learning Activity Data**: As you engage in lessons, quizzes, and general usage of the app, your activities will generate usage data, typically consisting of your learning patterns, studying traits, and answer history. This information is collected for analysis in aggregate, to improve the effectiveness of teaching and learning methods for all users of the platform.

**Speaking Questions**: Some lessons feature speaking portions where you are invited to submit an audio recording as a response to a question. To recognize speech, analyse pronunciation, and grade your response to this question your audio data may be transmitted to Tembo and shared with third-party providers (such as Apple or Google).

**Corrections Data**: Any questions or learning content that you flag as inaccurate will be stored and reported for the sole purpose of making improvements to the content we offer as a platform. This data may be subject to human review, but will not be associated with any of your other personal information, and will be removed as soon as possible.

**Log Data**: Information concerning requests you have made to access content from the Tembo platform are stored in a server access log, this data may include IP Addresses, Browser user agent, request path, time, status, and quantity of data transferred. Provided this data is not required for technical maintenance of the system, or for system security, then this data is regularly deleted and not associated with a particular user.

**Customer Service Data**: When you provide feedback on our service, contact our customer service, or support teams, we collect data that you provide to us. This may include your name, email address, and the content of the messages you send us. This information is used exclusively to address your inquiries, provide support, and improve our services.

3\. Information collected by third parties
------------------------------------------

**Google AdMob**: The Tembo App uses Google AdMob, as a mobile app advertising platform. To understand Google's use of Data, consult Google's partner policy. [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)

**Apple Speech Recognition Service**: Speech related questions utilize Apple Speech Recognition services to convert your voice data into text; your speech recordings may be retained on your device, but are not shared with Tembo. To understand Apples's use of speech data, consult Apple's dictation policy. [https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT210657](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT210657)

Your mobile device may provide controls that enable you to make choices about the collection of third-party data. (For example, see Apple iOSs advertising identifier and AdChoices). Opting out does not prevent the display of all advertisements.

4\. Data subject rights and data deletion
-----------------------------------------

You have the right to:

* Request access to personal data we hold on you. This enables you to export a copy of the personal information we hold on you.
* Request correction of personal data we hold on you. This enables you to update any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold on you.
* Request the deletion of your personal information.
* Withdraw consent for data processing where it was previously granted.
* To notify us of your intent to exercise your data subject rights please see the contact information below.

Please note, however, that we may need to retain certain information when we have a legal obligation or lawful basis to do so.

5\. Data Usage for Research, Artificial Intelligence, and Machine Learning
--------------------------------------------------------------------------

This section is dedicated to explaining how we may use the data we collect for research, artificial intelligence, and machine learning purposes.

**Data for Research**: We may use the data we collect to conduct research to enhance and improve our services, develop new services, and contribute to knowledge in fields related to our operations. The data used for such purposes will be anonymized and used in the aggregate, ensuring that individual user information cannot be identified or linked back to any specific person.

**Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning**: Our services employ Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) technologies to improve user experience and service functionality. The data collected may be used to train, test, and improve these AI and ML models. This may include understanding user preferences to provide personalized content or predictive text, improving the accuracy of our services, or developing new features.

Please note that when used for AI and ML purposes, the data is typically processed and stored in a de-identified, pseudonymized, or anonymized manner, ensuring the utmost privacy and confidentiality of our users' data. By using our services, you consent to the use of your data for these purposes. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please refer to Section 4 (Data subject rights and data deletion) for more information on how to do this.

6\. Children under the age of digital consent
---------------------------------------------

The Tembo platform is intended for users who have reached the age of digital consent, any use of the Tembo platform by users under the age of digital consent, even with the express permission of a parent/guardian is prohibited. Within the European Union, each member state is permitted to legally define its age of digital consent between the ages of 13 and 16, for users located outside of the European Union, your counties own age of digital consent should be used in place, in the event your own country does not define an age of digital consent, then the age of majority must be used in place.

If you become aware of any child using the Tembo platform before reaching the age of digital consent, please contact us using the details below, so that we may take the necessary actions.

7\. Security of your personal data
----------------------------------

The protection of your personal data holds great significance to us. It is crucial to note, however, that despite employing advanced encryption methods during data transmission and storage, no system on the Internet can guarantee 100% security.

We continuously enhance and update our security practices in response to new threats and advancements in technology to protect your personal data better. If you have any questions or concerns about the security of your data, please contact us.

8\. Contact
-----------

The trust of our users is important to us, therefore if you have any queries unanswered by this policy, or if you wish to notify us of your intent to exercise certain rights as a data subject, please contact us via email at the following address:

[\[email protected\]](https://www.tembo.app/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Site Language:** [English](https://www.tembo.app/), [Español](https://es.tembo.app/), [Deutsch](https://de.tembo.app/), [Français](https://fr.tembo.app/), [Português](https://pt.tembo.app/), [Русский](https://ru.tembo.app/), [中文(简体)](https://zh.tembo.app/), [عربي](https://ar.tembo.app/), [हिंदी](https://hi.tembo.app/), [日本語](https://ja.tembo.app/),

Tembo © 2024
